<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legaldoc>

<name id="Agreement">
 <content>By visiting our Websites, contacting us or using the Services, you (1) acknowledge and agree that you have read and understand these Terms of Use, (2) agree to be bound by them, and (3) that you have the ability and authority to accept them.</content>
 <smallprint>If you do not agree with these Terms of Use or are unable to accept them, you are not authorized to register or continue to use your account. Please delete your account and do not use Websites or Services.</smallprint> 
</name>

<name id="Parents">
 <content>TaGaJo strives to create the best and safest play experiences for gamers of all ages. To that end, we require that those wishing to create an account that requires the collection of personally identifiable information must be at least thirteen (13) years old, or have their parent or guardian's express written consent. Please be aware that certain areas of the Websites and certain portion of the Services may contain or provide access to more mature types of content. You may be exposed to some content that you find offensive, indecent, or objectionable. By visiting our Websites or using our Services, you assume all risk. We encourage parents to supervise their children's use of our Websites and Services and maintain open communication regarding appropriate materials for use and viewing by their children.</content>
 <smallprint></smallprint>
</name>

<name id="General Terms">
 <content>1. Account Subscription.
a. Registration. While some elements of the Websites may be accessible to the public, certain aspects of the Services (e.g., creating a community profile, acquiring a subscription to DandD Insider, posting in forums as well as participating in organized play) require that you register an account. To register an account, you will asked to provide your date of birth and country/region, and then provide your email address as well a username, a screen name and a password; however, to gain access to certain Services (e.g., organized play, invitations to special events, forums, promotions, and prize payments), you may be asked to provide your full name, address, city, state, and country. You agree to: (i) provide accurate, current and complete information about you as may be prompted by any registration forms for the Services ("Registration Data"); and (ii) maintain and promptly update the Registration Data, and any other account-related information you provide to TaGaJo.</content>
 <smallprint></smallprint>
</name>

<name id="Passwords">
 <content>b. Passwords; Security. You are entirely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password, and you agree to maintain the security of your password. You also agree not to share your account, screen name, username or password, and agree to notify TaGaJo immediately if you suspect any unauthorized use of your account. You further agree that you are entirely liable for all activities conducted through your account, and are responsible for ensuring that you or your child is aware of, understands, and complies with these Terms of Use and all other rules, policies, or notices published by TaGaJo.</content>
 <smallprint>TaGaJo employees will never ask for your password!</smallprint>
</name>

<name id="Eligibility">
 <content>c. Eligibility. Use of the Services is void where prohibited. By registering an account and using the Services, you represent and warrant that: (i) all Registration Data that you submit is truthful and accurate; (ii) you are thirteen (13) years old or older or have your parenl or guardian's consent as demonstrated by submittal of the appropriate paperwork (available at http://media.TaGaJo.com/downloads/TaGaJoaccount/coppaTaGaJoparentalconsentform_en.pdf) by such parent or guardian; and (iii) your use of the Services does not violate, and you will not use the Services to facilitate the violation of, any applicable law or regulation, these Terms of Use, or any other rules, policies, or notices published by TaGaJo. Your account may be deleted and your access to the Services terminated without warning if we believe that you are under thirteen (13) years old and are using the Services without parental/guardian permission. Please note that the purchase or use of certain Services may have different eligibility requirements, including a higher minimum age requirements, as specified in any additional terms governing such Services.</content>
 <smallprint></smallprint>
</name>

<name id="Use of Websites and Services">
 <content>2. Use of Websites and Services.
a. License. Subject to your compliance with these Terms of Use, the Websites, Services, "fan kits" policies, play test materials and other TaGaJo' offerings are provided to you on a nonexclusive, fully revocable basis for your individual, non-commercial use solely for entertainment purposes.</content>
 <smallprint>The Websites and Services are for your personal use and may not be used in connection with any commercial endeavors. Illegal or unauthorized use of the Websites or Services including collecting players' usernames or email addresses for the purpose of sending unsolicited email is strictly prohibited. Commercial advertisements (via emails, forums, etc.) and other forms of solicitation in violation of these Terms of Use may be removed from the Websites and Services without notice and may result in termination of your account.</smallprint>
</name>

<name id="Waiver and Consent">
 <content>Waiver and Consent. By participating in organized play events you agree to the following:

    You agree to comply with all rules, regulations, and behavior standards applicable to the event you participate in, as may be modified from time to time in TaGaJo' sole discretion. You understand and agree that all decisions of TaGaJo and its authorized representatives, independent tournament organizers ("ITOs"), and judges with respect to such an event are final.</content>
 <smallprint>YOU AGREE TO RELEASE, INDEMNIFY, AND HOLD TaGaJo, EVENT AFFILIATES AND ITOs HARMLESS FROM ANY AND ALL LOSS, INJURY, DAMAGE, CLAIM, AND ACTION OF ANY KIND IN CONNECTION WITH OR ARISING FROM YOUR PARTICIPATION IN AN EVENT (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, JUDGING DECISIONS) OR ANY AWARD INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, PERSONAL INJURIES, DEATH, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR CLAIMS BASED ON PUBLICITY RIGHTS, DEFAMATION, OR INVASION OF PRIVACY, WHETHER SUFFERED BY ME OR A THIRD PARTY, HOWEVER CAUSED, AND WHETHER FORESEEN OR UNFORESEEN. TaGaJo, ITS EVENT AFFILIATES, AND ITOs ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR INJURY OR DAMAGE OF ANY KIND RELATED TO OR RESULTING FROM PARTICIPATION IN THE EVENT.</smallprint>
</name>

<name id="Feedback">
 <content>Feedback. You acknowledge and agree that any materials, including but not limited to, questions, comments, suggestions, ideas, plans, notes, drawings, original or creative materials or other information, provided by you in the form of email or other submissions to TaGaJo in response to a request for such materials ("Feedback") are non-confidential and shall become the sole property of TaGaJo. This paragraph is not intended to apply to any personal information about you (such as name, mailing address and e-mail address), the use and disclosure of which is described in TaGaJo' Privacy Policy.</content>
 <smallprint>Constructive criticism please!</smallprint>
</name>

</legaldoc>
